http://www.surveillance-video.com/privacypolicy

Search:
800-955-5201
Menu
loading...
view quote
items loading...
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Complete Systems
2 Camera Systems4 Camera Systems6 Camera Systems8 Camera Systems16 Camera SystemsView All Kits
Recording
Digital Video RecordersSD-DEF,HD Recorders,Network Video Recorders
Capture Cards4 Ch,8 Ch,16 Ch,32 Ch
Recording AccessoriesHarddrives,Expansion Bays,Expansion Cards
Monitors
LCD Monitors19 inch,32 inch,42 inchLED Monitors19 inch,32 inch,42 inch
Monitor AccessoriesMonitor Adaptors,TurnableDigital Signage MonitorsField MonitorsComposite,HDMI,RCA,VGAPublic View Monitors9.7 inch,19 inch,32 inch
Network
IP CamerasIndoor,Vandal Resistant,Weather ResistantNVR4 Channel,8 Channel,16 ChannelSoftware4 Channel,8 Channel,16 ChannelNetwork Switches4 Port,8 Port,16 Port
Transmission
Wireless TransmissionAntennas,Receivers,TransmittersEncoders & DecodersDecoders,Encoders
MatrixSwitchers,Components,Keyboards & ControllersData TransmissionConverters,Extenders,RepeatersFiber Optic TransmissionConverters,Receivers,TransmittersUTP Transmission & BalunsPower, Video, Data UTP,Audio & Video UTPVideo DistributionConverters,Digital Signage,Distribution Amplifier
Security
Burglar AlarmsKits,Sensors,AccessoriesDetectionDIY Detection,Pro Detection,Premier DetectionGPS TrackingAccess ControlKits,Cards & Accessories,Controllers & Modules,Locks
Audio
SpeakersPA Speakers,Recessed Speakers,Two Way SpeakersRecording DevicesCovert,StandardMicrophonesIntercomsMaster Stations,Entrance Panels,AccessoriesAudio KitAudio Surveillance,Intercom KitsAudio AdaptersAudio MixersListening DevicesAudio Counter SurveillanceAudio ModulesPA & Ambient Audio
Accessories
ConnectorsWire Connectors,Adaptors,PigtailsInstallation Tools & SuppliesTools,Wire,HardwareCamera AccessoriesCamera Lenses,Bubbles & Cages
Keyboard ControllersKeyboard Joysticks,Keypads,Keyboards
Infrared IlluminatorsInvisible,Semi-covert,Standard,White LEDMountsCamera Brackets,Illuminators,Mobile,MonitorsLens AccessoriesLens Cleaning,Lens Rings,Extension TubesEnclosuresCamera housings,Door StationsPTZ ScannersIndoor,OutdoorPOS Integration
Power
Surveillance Power ProductsPower Supplies,Back-Up Power Supplies (UPS),Surge Protection PoE ProductsPoE Adaptors,PoE Midspans,PoE SplittersAccess Control Power productsAccess Control Power supplies,Access Power Controllers,Batteries Fire & Life SafetyNAC Power Extenders,BatteriesAutomation & SecurityPower Supply Chargers,Relay Modules,Timer Modules
Home Automation
Dimmers & Switches Kits & Hubs Thermostats Accessories Smart Locks Alarm Systems Appliances Cameras Doorbells Outlets Sensors Intercoms
Brands
A
ACTi
Active Vision
Adams Rite
AG Neovo
Aiphone
Alpha
Complete Systems
2 Camera Systems4 Camera Systems6 Camera Systems8 Camera Systems16 Camera SystemsView All Kits
Cameras
Dome CamerasHigh Def,Network IP,Analog
Auto Mobile CamerasHigh Def,Network IP,Analog
180º - 360º CamerasAnalog,Network IP,Vandal Resistant
Bullet CamerasHigh Def,Network IP,Analog
Corner/Wedge CamerasHigh Def,Network IP,Analog
Covert CamerasHigh Def,Network IP,Analog
Box CamerasHigh Def,Network IP,Analog
License Plate CamerasHigh Def,Network IP,Analog
Mini board CamerasHigh Def,Network IP,Analog
PTZ CamerasHigh Def,Network IP,Analog
Thermal Imaging CamerasNetwork IP,Analog,Weather Resistant
Wireless CamerasNetwork IP,Analog,Weather Resistant
Recording
Digital Video RecordersSD-DEF,HD Recorders,Network Video Recorders
Network Video Recorders4 Channel,8 Channel,16 Channel
HD RecordersHD TVI,HD SDI,HD CVI
Hybrid RecordersAnalog/HD-SDI,Analog/Network
Recording SoftwareAnalytics,Managment,Upgrades
Capture Cards4 Ch,8 Ch,16 Ch,32 Ch
Recording AccessoriesHarddrives,Expansion Bays,Expansion Cards
Monitors
LCD Monitors19 inch,32 inch,42 inchLED Monitors19 inch,32 inch,42 inch
Monitor AccessoriesMonitor Adaptors,TurnableDigital Signage MonitorsField MonitorsComposite,HDMI,RCA,VGAPublic View Monitors9.7 inch,19 inch,32 inch
Network
IP CamerasIndoor,Vandal Resistant,Weather ResistantNVR4 Channel,8 Channel,16 ChannelSoftware4 Channel,8 Channel,16 ChannelNetwork Switches4 Port,8 Port,16 Port
Transmission
Wireless TransmissionAntennas,Receivers,TransmittersEncoders & DecodersDecoders,Encoders
MatrixSwitchers,Components,Keyboards & ControllersData TransmissionConverters,Extenders,RepeatersFiber Optic TransmissionConverters,Receivers,TransmittersUTP Transmission & BalunsPower, Video, Data UTP,Audio & Video UTPVideo DistributionConverters,Digital Signage,Distribution Amplifier
Security
Burglar AlarmsKits,Sensors,AccessoriesDetectionDIY Detection,Pro Detection,Premier DetectionGPS TrackingAccess ControlKits,Cards & Accessories,Controllers & Modules,Locks
Audio
SpeakersPA Speakers,Recessed Speakers,Two Way SpeakersRecording DevicesCovert,StandardMicrophonesIntercomsMaster Stations,Entrance Panels,AccessoriesAudio KitAudio Surveillance,Intercom KitsAudio AdaptersAudio MixersListening DevicesAudio Counter SurveillanceAudio ModulesPA & Ambient Audio
Accessories
ConnectorsWire Connectors,Adaptors,PigtailsInstallation Tools & SuppliesTools,Wire,HardwareCamera AccessoriesCamera Lenses,Bubbles & Cages
Keyboard ControllersKeyboard Joysticks,Keypads,Keyboards
Infrared IlluminatorsInvisible,Semi-covert,Standard,White LEDMountsCamera Brackets,Illuminators,Mobile,MonitorsLens AccessoriesLens Cleaning,Lens Rings,Extension TubesEnclosuresCamera housings,Door StationsPTZ ScannersIndoor,OutdoorPOS Integration
Power
Surveillance Power ProductsPower Supplies,Back-Up Power Supplies (UPS),Surge Protection PoE ProductsPoE Adaptors,PoE Midspans,PoE SplittersAccess Control Power productsAccess Control Power supplies,Access Power Controllers,Batteries Fire & Life SafetyNAC Power Extenders,BatteriesAutomation & SecurityPower Supply Chargers,Relay Modules,Timer Modules
Home Automation
Dimmers & SwitchesKit HubsThermostatsAccessoriesSmart Locks
Brands
Home
Privacy Policy
Product was successfully added to your shopping cart.
View Cart
Keep Shopping
Privacy Policy
Information Collection & Use
Surveillance Video is the sole owner of the information collected on www.Surveillance-Video.com. Surveillance Video collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.
We collect personally identifiable information on our site at places including Become A Dealer, Request A Quote, Contact Us, Catalogue Request and Newsletter sign up. We collect information such as name, address, email address, business name, etc.
Surveys or Contests
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).
We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes and to monitor site traffic.
We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing.
Forward To A Friend
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Surveillance Video does not store this information.
Message Board/Forum and BLOG
If you use our message board/forum or blog on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. Please note that although you will be on hostingprod.com’s site when on our BLOG, our privacy policy governs the collection and use of your data while on our BLOG.
Note that we also have a member list function within our Forum. Members automatically are included in this list. They can, however, choose to have their email remain private when signing up for the forum. Much of the information collected during registration is optional. Personal information is used only if a member needs to be contacted for any reason and is not given out to any third parties.
Uses of Information
Surveillance Video collects information that users submit for the purposes of shipping and billing of a customer’s order. Surveillance Users can sign up to receive periodic newsletters; this process includes the submittal of a user’s email address. Personal information is also collected when a user requests a quote in order to reply to that user. Information is collected when users apply for dealer status in order to verify that said users are resellers. Personal information is collected when users sign up for a catalog request in order to facilitate this request.
Communications from the Site
Special Offers and Updates We will occasionally send you information on special deals and promotions. You can sign up for these offers by sending an email toinfo@Surveillance-Video.com.
Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.”
Newsletters
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.
Service-related Announcements
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.
You may opt-out of these communications. Please see “Choice and Opt-out.”
Customer Service
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
We do not share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers.
We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.
Personally identifiable information:
We Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties. This sharing occurs when we ship your order and when we process your credit card. We also use a third party for web hosting.
Agents
We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
Service Providers
We use other third parties to provide hosting services for our Web site. We will share contact information as necessary for the third party to provide that service.
These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing.
Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
Choice/Opt-out
Users must choose to sign up for the newsletter; it is not automatically sent to them. Surveys are also optional.
We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at info@Surveillance-Video.com.
You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.
Log Files
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our shopping cart. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.
We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.
If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as the shopping cart, will be limited.
Some of our business partners (e.g., tracking utilities) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.
We use a third-party tracking service called Clearsaleing that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. We collect information such as how the user came to our site and what items a user purchased to better understand our marketing strategy.
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.surveillance-video.com only.
Links to Other Sites
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Surveillance Video. Please be aware that we, Surveillance Video, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. Please also note that while on our BLOG (hosted on a third party site) that in this instance our privacy policy governs these pages. See “Message Board/Forum and BLOG” above for more information).
This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.
Testimonials/Reviews
When you offer us a testimonial or a review during checkout or offline we receive permission to post prior to posting.
Access to Personally Identifiable Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update, or delete it by emailing our Customer Support at info@Surveillance-Video.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as Tax ID number on the Dealer Signup forms), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL)
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at info@Surveillance-Video.com.
Changes in this Privacy Statement
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: info@Surveillance-Video.com or http://www.surveillance-video.com/contact.html.
Surveillance-Video
387 Canal Street
NY, NY 10013
Tel. 1.800.955.5201
Fax. 1.212.431.2622
Also of InterestWireless Transmitters & ReceiversVoice DialerConverters
Customer Service Call or email today to speak with one of our customer service specialists
Technical Support Call or email today to speak with one of our customer service specialists
Working Days/Hours:
Thank you, we have received your request. A customer support representative will contact you shortly.
